{"testId":"-OjQpyiwad5nMKgs_kS7","userId":"ifbu","date":"2026_01_28","responses":[{"question":{"questionText":"No matter how far you stand from a mirror, your image is always erect. The mirror is most likely to be - ","option1":"Plane mirror","option2":"Concave mirror","option3":"Convex mirror","option4":"Either plane or convex","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":4},{"question":{"questionText":"Which one of the following is the correct sequence in the order decreasing the length of three structural part given below of the small intestine in the human body?","option1":"Jejunum - Duodenum - Ileum","option2":"Ileum - Duodenum - Jejunum","option3":"Jejunum - Ileum - Duodenum","option4":"Ileam - Jejunum - Duodenum","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":2},{"question":{"questionText":"Aluminium powder is used in thermite welding as it is a _______.","option1":"A strong oxidising agent","option2":"A strong reducing agent","option3":"Corrosion Resistant","option4":"Good Conductor of heat","correctOption":"2"},"responseCode":2},{"question":{"questionText":"Which of the following elements do not show tetravalency?","option1":"Ge","option2":"Si","option3":"C","option4":"O","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":4},{"question":{"questionText":"Identify the option that indicates the correct function or purpose served by cotyledon, plumule and radical respectively.","option1":"Future shoot, future root, store food","option2":"Future root, future shoot, store food","option3":"Store food, future shoot, future root","option4":"Future root, Store food, Future shoot","correctOption":"3"},"responseCode":3}]}
{"testId":"-OjQpyiwad5nMKgs_kS7","userId":"odnsf","date":"2026_01_28","responses":[{"question":{"questionText":"Aluminium powder is used in thermite welding as it is a _______.","option1":"A strong oxidising agent","option2":"A strong reducing agent","option3":"Corrosion Resistant","option4":"Good Conductor of heat","correctOption":"2"},"responseCode":2},{"question":{"questionText":"Which of the following elements do not show tetravalency?","option1":"Ge","option2":"Si","option3":"C","option4":"O","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":4},{"question":{"questionText":"Which one of the following is the correct sequence in the order decreasing the length of three structural part given below of the small intestine in the human body?","option1":"Jejunum - Duodenum - Ileum","option2":"Ileum - Duodenum - Jejunum","option3":"Jejunum - Ileum - Duodenum","option4":"Ileam - Jejunum - Duodenum","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":2},{"question":{"questionText":"No matter how far you stand from a mirror, your image is always erect. The mirror is most likely to be - ","option1":"Plane mirror","option2":"Concave mirror","option3":"Convex mirror","option4":"Either plane or convex","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":4},{"question":{"questionText":"Identify the option that indicates the correct function or purpose served by cotyledon, plumule and radical respectively.","option1":"Future shoot, future root, store food","option2":"Future root, future shoot, store food","option3":"Store food, future shoot, future root","option4":"Future root, Store food, Future shoot","correctOption":"3"},"responseCode":3}]}
{"testId":"-OjQpyiwad5nMKgs_kS7","userId":null,"date":"2026_01_28","responses":[{"question":{"questionText":"Which of the following elements do not show tetravalency?","option1":"Ge","option2":"Si","option3":"C","option4":"O","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":4}]}
{"testId":"-OjQpyiwad5nMKgs_kS7","userId":"admin","date":"2026_01_28","responses":[{"question":{"questionText":"Which of the following elements do not show tetravalency?","option1":"Ge","option2":"Si","option3":"C","option4":"O","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":4},{"question":{"questionText":"Aluminium powder is used in thermite welding as it is a _______.","option1":"A strong oxidising agent","option2":"A strong reducing agent","option3":"Corrosion Resistant","option4":"Good Conductor of heat","correctOption":"2"},"responseCode":2},{"question":{"questionText":"No matter how far you stand from a mirror, your image is always erect. The mirror is most likely to be - ","option1":"Plane mirror","option2":"Concave mirror","option3":"Convex mirror","option4":"Either plane or convex","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":4},{"question":{"questionText":"Which one of the following is the correct sequence in the order decreasing the length of three structural part given below of the small intestine in the human body?","option1":"Jejunum - Duodenum - Ileum","option2":"Ileum - Duodenum - Jejunum","option3":"Jejunum - Ileum - Duodenum","option4":"Ileam - Jejunum - Duodenum","correctOption":"4"},"responseCode":2},{"question":{"questionText":"Identify the option that indicates the correct function or purpose served by cotyledon, plumule and radical respectively.","option1":"Future shoot, future root, store food","option2":"Future root, future shoot, store food","option3":"Store food, future shoot, future root","option4":"Future root, Store food, Future shoot","correctOption":"3"},"responseCode":3}]}
